<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pineapple Lock Screen</string>
    <string name="app_launcher_name">Lock Screen</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_label">Pineapple Lock Screen - Accessibility Service</string>
    <string name="tile_service_label">Lock Screen</string>
    <string name="shortcut_name_lock">Lock</string>
    <string name="fab_lock_screen">Lock Screen</string>
    <string name="open_source_licenses">Open Source Licenses</string>
    <string name="current_version">Current Version</string>
    <string name="card_a11y_description">This application require to enable its accessibility service in order to work.\nYou can use the following button to enable or disable the service conveniently.</string>
    <string name="card_a11y_action_go_to_setting">Accessibility Settings</string>
    <string name="card_shortcut_description">You can create a shortcut icon on your launcher to perform the lock action.</string>
    <string name="card_shortcut_action_create_shortcut">Create Shortcut Icon</string>
    <string name="msg_pls_enable_a11y_service_first">Please enable its accessibility service first</string>
    <string name="msg_action_open_a11y_settings">Open Settings</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_description">This accessibility service is used to provide the lock screen ability in the Pineapple Lock Screen application, otherwise the application won\'t be able to work.\n\nTo enable the accessibility service, just tap the toggle switch in the top right corner, then tap Allow on the next screen. You don\'t need to enable the second shortcut switch.\n\nNote:\n1. If you force stop the main application, you might need to enable this service again.\n2. If the service is enabled but the application doesn\'t work as intended, try disable and enable it again.</string>
    <string name="shortcut_name_powerdialog">Power Dialog</string>
    <string name="menu">Menu</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_prominent_disclosure_dlg_title">About Accessibility Service Permission</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_prominent_disclosure_dlg_desc">This application uses the Accessibility Service to provide the lock screen functionality. Related service needs to be enabled to work.\n\nYou can use the entrance link in the main screen to access the accessibility setting at any time you want.\n\nThis application doesn\'t collect any user data. You can also review the full content of Privacy Policy in the About screen.</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="option_use_compat_method">Use compat shortcut method</string>
    <string name="option_use_compat_method_short_desc">When creating shortcut from widgets</string>
    <string name="option_use_compat_method_long_desc">In some launchers, if you drag a shortcut from the widget list to the home screen, you can create a shortcut icon without the application icon displayed in the corner when using the compat method.</string>
    <string name="source_code">Source Code</string>
    <string name="option_battery_optimization">Battery optimization option</string>
    <string name="option_battery_optimization_short_desc">Consider disable it for this application</string>
    <string name="option_battery_optimization_long_desc">Some phone models/ROM may have very restrictive battery optimization functions which will result application service get killed in the background. Every time this application get killed, you\'ll need to enable its accessibility service again.\n\n To prevent this, you can disable Battery optimization for this application via system Settings screen by:\n \n 1. Select All apps in the dropdown\n 2. Select Pineapple Lock Screen then switch off or choose Don\'t optimize\n \nThis setting is only needed when your ROM keep killing the service of this application, you don\'t need to do anything if it works fine. Providing the ability of locking screen is the only thing that the service of this application will do. This won\'t affact your battery life.</string>
    <string name="card_qstile_description">This application also provide a quick settings tile to turn the screen off. You can add the tile by edit the quick settings area and drag the Lock Screen tile to where you want.</string>
    <string name="card_qstile_action_open_qs">Open Quick Settings</string>
    <string name="rate_us">Rate Us</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="app_widget_description">Resizable widget for locking screen</string>
    <string name="loading_widget">Loading</string>
    <string name="app_widget_name">Lock Screen Widget</string>
    <string name="get_plus_version">Get Plus Version</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="contribute_translation">Contribute Translation</string>
    <string name="option_use_launcher_icon_to_lock">Use application icon to lock</string>
    <string name="option_use_launcher_icon_to_lock_desc">Tap the app icon to lock the screen</string>
    <string name="option_use_launcher_icon_to_lock_long_desc">Once this option is enabled, when accessibility service is enabled, you can then use this application\'s default icon to lock the screen.\n\nThis option is in case the compact method no longer works on newer android version and for users that don\'t want to have a badge icon on the shortcuts that they created.\n\nOnce enabled, you can still access the Settings screen to disable the option by tap and hold the default application icon to open the shortcut menu, and choose the Settings shortcut menu option.</string>
</resources>